casualsexgroup.com 2010-11-20

# Casual Sex Group: Join Right Now for FREE. Search through thousands of LOCAL PROFILES on CasualSexGroup.com

**Privacy Statement for SexDateNetwork**

SexDateNetwork has created this Privacy Statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to helping our users better understand what information we collect about them and what may happen to that information.

The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website: SexDateNetwork.

**Overview**

As part of the normal operation of our services we collect, but do not disclose information about you. This Privacy Policy describes the information we collect about you and what may happen to that information.

By accepting this Privacy Policy and our Terms and Conditions, you expressly consent to our use of your personal information in the manner prescribed in this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and subject to the terms of the SexDateNetwork Terms and Conditions.

The privacy practices of this statement apply to the SexDateNetwork web site (the 'Site').

**1\. A Special Note About Children**

Children are not eligible to use our services, and we ask that minors (under the age of 18) do not submit any personal information to us.

**2\. Information We Collect**

Our primary goal in collecting personal information is to provide you with a smooth, efficient, and customized experience. This allows us to provide services and features that most likely meet your needs and to customize our service to make your experience easier. Your name is confidential and will not be posted in your profile. Your profile is available for other members to view on the Site. Members' profiles include a description and photos, likes and dislikes, individual essays and other information helpful in determining matches. Your viewable profile does not include any identifying information about you, except the Username you chose upon registering. When you send an introductory note through our system to another member, your email address is included in that note so that the recipient can respond to you.

Under some circumstances we may require some additional information, such as, but not limited to credit card details. We use this financial information, including your name, address, and other information, as well as to bill you for use of our services.

We automatically track certain information based upon your behavior on our site using cookies and other devices. We use this information to internal research on our members' demographics, interests, and behavior to better understand and serve you and our community. This information may include the URL that you just came from (whether this URL is on our site or not). Which URL you next go to (whether this URL is on our site or not), what browser you are using, and your IP address.

We use data collection devices such as "cookies" on certain pages of our site. "Cookies" are small files placed on your hard drive that assist us in providing customized services. We also offer certain features that are only available through the use of a "cookie". Most cookies are "session cookies", meaning that they are automatically deleted from your hard drive at the end of a session. You are always free to decline our cookies if your browser permits.

**3\. Our Use of Your Information**

We use information in the files we maintain about you, and the other information we obtain from your current and past activities on the Site to resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems and enforce our Terms and Conditions. At times, we may look across multiple members to identify problems or resolve disputes, and in particular we may examine your information to identify members multiple Member ID No. or aliases.

You agree that we may use personally identifiable information about you to improve our marketing and promotional efforts, to analyze site usage, improve our content and product offerings, and customize our Site's content, layout, and services. These uses improve our site and better tailor it to meet your needs.

You agree that we may use your information to contact you and deliver information to you that, in some cases, are targeted to your interests, such as targeted banner advertisements, administrative notices, product offerings, and communications relevant to your use of the Site. By accepting Privacy Policy, you expressly agree to receive this information. If you do not wish to receive these communications, we encourage you to opt out of the receipt of certain communications by sending an email to support[AT]sexdatenetwork.com.

You agree that we may transfer personally identifiable information about you to third party marketing partners who may then contact you based on that information.

**4\. Our Disclosure of Your Information**

Due to the existing regulatory environment, we cannot ensure that all of your private communications and other personally identifiable information will never be disclosed in ways not otherwise described in this Privacy Policy. By way of example (without limiting and foregoing), we may be forced to disclose information to the government, law enforcement agencies or third parties under certain circumstances, third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications, or members may abuse or misuse your information that they collect from our Site. Therefore, although we use industry standard practices to protect your privacy, we do not promise, and you should not expect, that your personally identifiable information or private communications will always remain private.

The following describes some of the ways that your personally identifiable information may be disclosed.

Legal Requests. SexDateNetwork cooperates with law enforcement inquiries, as well as other third parties to enforce laws, such as: intellectual property rights, fraud and other rights. We can (and you authorize us to) disclose any information about you to law enforcement and other government officials as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate, in connection with an investigation of fraud, intellectual property infringements, or other activity that is illegal or may expose us or you to legal liability.

**5\. Your Use of other Members Information**

In order to facilitate interaction among all our members, when you send an introductory note through our system to another member, your email address is included in that note so that the recipient can respond to you. We also allow you access to our chat room. As a member you have access to the Members ID No., and you might gain access to other contact information of the Member(s) through the regular use of the chat room. By accepting this Privacy Policy, you agree that, with respect to other Members' personally identifiable information that you obtain through the email communication and the chat room, SexDateNetwork hereby grants to you a license to use such information only for: (a) SexDateNetwork related communications that are not unsolicited commercial messages, and (b) any other purpose that such member expressly agrees to after adequate disclosure of the purpose(s). In all cases, you must give Members an opportunity to remove themselves from your database and a chance to review what information you have collected about them. In addition, under no circumstances, except as defined in this Section, can you disclose personally identifiable information about another member to any third party without our consent and the consent of such other member after adequate disclosure. SexDateNetwork and our members do not tolerate spam. Therefore, without limiting the foregoing, you are not licensed to add a SexDateNetwork member, to your mail list (email or physical mail) without their express written consent after adequate disclosure. To report spam from other SexDateNetwork members, please send an email at support[at]sexdatenetwork.com.

**6\. Accessing, Reviewing and Changing Your Profile**

Following registration, you can review and change the information you submitted during registration through the Member Service Menu including: Your password and e-mail address. If you change your password and email we keep track of your old password and email. You can also change your registration information such as: name, address, city, state, zip code, country, phone number, profile, likes and dislikes, desired date profile, essays and saves search criteria.

Upon your written request, we will suspend your membership, contact information, and financial information from our active databases. Such information will be suspended as soon as reasonably possible in accordance with our suspension policy and applicable law.

We will retain our files information you have requested to remove in order in some circumstances, such as to resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems and enforce our terms and conditions. Further, such prior information is never completely removed from our databases due to technical and legal constraints, including stored ‘back up' systems. Therefore, you should not expect that all of your personally identifiable information will be completely removed from our databases in response to your requests.

**7\. Control of Your Password**

You are responsible for all actions taken with your member ID No. and password, including fees. Therefore we do not recommend that you disclose your SexDateNetwork password or member ID No. to any third parties. If you choose to share your member ID No and password or your information with third parties to provide you additional services, you are responsible for all actions taken with your member ID No. and password and therefore should review that third party's privacy policy. If you lose control of your password, you may lose substantial control over your personally identifiable information and may be subject to legally binding actions taken on your behalf. Therefore, if your password has been compromised for any reason, you should immediately change your password.

**8\. Other Information Collectors**

Except as otherwise expressly included in this Privacy Policy, this document only addresses the use and disclosure of information we collect from you. To the extent that you disclose your information to other parties, whether they are on our Site or on other sites throughout the Internet, different rules may apply to their use or disclosure of the information you disclose to them. To the extent that we use third party advertisers, they adhere to their own privacy policies. Since SexDateNetwork does not control the privacy policies of the third parties, you are subject to ask questions before you disclose your personal information to others.

**9\. Security**

SexDateNetwork uses industry standard practices to safeguard the confidentiality of your personal identifiable information, including "firewalls" and Secure Socket Layers. SexDateNetwork treats data as an asset that must be protected against loss and unauthorized access. We employ many different security techniques to protect such data from unauthorized access by members inside and outside the company. However, "perfect security" does not exist on the Internet.

**10\. Notice**

We may change this Privacy Policy from the time based on your comments and our need to accurately reflect our data collection and disclosure practices. All changes to this policy are effective immediately upon posting the changes to our website.
